A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Comptroller, Program Management Cost Files FA501
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Management Costs, 1961-1984; III
  - NA/SD -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NA/UMD -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - OA -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - OA -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - OCOMM -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - OCOMM -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - RE -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs (PA 76-980), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - RE -- FY 1976 Program Management Costs, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1977 General Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ADMIN and FA -- FY 1977 Special Retrenchment Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1977 General Management Costs, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - E and R -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - E and R -- FY 1977 Administrative File -- Malcolm Moos Consultancy on the Urban University (MCA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - FA -- FY 1977 Financial Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 77-980, MCA 778-0980), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1977 Attachment File -- OLAC Program Plans and Funding Request Report (PA 77-980) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1977 Quarterly Budget Projections, Related Memos (PA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1977 Mid-Year Reviews (PA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1977 Memos Re: Program Management Budget, Summaries of OLAC Program Activities, etc. (PA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 77-980, MCA 778-0980), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1977 Attachment File -- Report: Evaluation of Development Economics Program at the University of Ife (PA 77-980, 778-0980) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1977 Attachment File -- Report: Resources in West Africa for Intensive Training in English and French (PA 77-980, 778-0980), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1977 Nairobi -- Memo Re: David Jones Visit to New York (PA 77-980), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 77-0980, MCA 778-0980), 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - NA -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - OA -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - OCOMM -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (MCA 77-980), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - RE -- FY 1977 Program Management Costs (PA 778-980), 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1978 General Management Costs (PA 78-980), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1978 Special Retrenchment Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1978 General Management Costs (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - E and R -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (MCA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - E and R/PPSO -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - FA -- FY 1978 Financial Management Costs (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, with Correspondence (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1978 Attachment File -- Report: Social Science Research and Public Policy in India (PA78-980, AP-IR6) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA78-980), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Attachment File -- Memorandum and Documents Summarizing Budget Deliberations (PA78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Attachment File -- Report: Program Plans and Funding Request... (PA 78-980) (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Attachment File -- Report: Program Plans and Funding Request... (PA 78-980) (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Quarterly Budget Projections (PA 78-980) (1 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Quarterly Budget Projections (PA 78-980) (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Quarterly Budget Projections (PA 78-980) (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Memos Re: Bogota Field Office Audit, Change in Cost of Living Allowance, etc. (PA 78-980) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Memos Re: Recent Problems with Grant Processing and Payments, Bank Transfers, etc. (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1978 Mid-Year Reviews (PA 78-980) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA 78-980, MCA 788-0980), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA 78-980, MCA 788-0980), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1978 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: Population Office Library (PA 78-984, 788-0984) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - NA -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (PA 78-980, MCA 78-980), 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - OA -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (MCA 78-980), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Office of Communications (OCOMM) -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - RE -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs (788-980), 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - RE -- FY 1978 Program Management Costs, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - ADMIN, OP, OR and OSGC -- FY 1979 General Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - E and R -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (MCA 79-980), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - FA -- FY 1979 Financial Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - ID -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - International Division/Asia and Pacific -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980, MCA 798-0980), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1979 Attachment File -- Report: Management Costs: Proposed Budget Fiscal Year 1979 (PA 79-980), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1979 Quarterly Budget Projections, etc. (PA 79-980) (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1979 Quarterly Budget Projections, etc. (PA 79-980) (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980, MCA 798-0980), 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1979 Attachment File -- Memos Re: Social Sciences in Nigeria, etc., 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980, MCA 798-0980), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1979 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: Requests for Population Information, etc. (PA 79-984), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - NA -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (MCA 79-980), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - OA -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (MCA 79-980), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Office of Communications (OCOMM) -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (MCA 79-980), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - PPSO -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (MCA 799-980), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - RE -- FY 1979 Program Management Costs (PA 79-980), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - ADMIN -- FY 1980 General Management Costs (PA 80-980, 808-0980), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - EPP/E and R -- FY 1980 Administrative File -- Board of Trustees Approved Actions, etc. (MCA 80-980), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - FA -- FY 1980 Financial Management Costs (PA 80-980, 808-0980), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (PA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (MCA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (PA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1980 Attachment File -- OLAC Budget Documents (PA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1980 Quarterly Budget Projections (PA 80-980) (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1980 Quarterly Budget Projections (PA 80-980) (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (MCA 80-980), 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - ID/OVP -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (PA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (MCA 80-980), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1980 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: Population Information Requests (PA 80-980) (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1980 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: Population Information Requests (PA 80-984) (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NA -- FY 1980 Program Management Costs (PA 80-980), 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Education and Public Policy (EPP) -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (PA 81-980), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - ID/AP -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (PA 81-980), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (MCA 81-980), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ID/EIA -- FY 1981 Staff Folder -- Carlos F. Diaz Alejandro Correspondence Re: Trip to England (MCA 81-980) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - ID/LAC -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (PA 81-980), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (MCA 81-980), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - ID/MEA -- FY 1981 Consultants -- Robert W. Kerwin Evaluation of Science Education Program in Turkey, 1960-1980 (MCA 819-980) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (MCA 81-980) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1981 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: FF Population Grants, Grants Reporting, etc. (PA 81-984), 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - NA -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (PA 81-980) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - OA -- FY 1981 Program Management Costs (MCA 81-980) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Developing Countries Program (DCP) -- FY 1982 Program Support Management Costs (PA 828-980) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - ID/POP -- FY 1982 Attachment File -- Tim Rice Memos Re: Population Information Requests (PA 828-984), 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - United States and International Affairs Program/Human Rights and Governance (USIAP/HRG) -- FY 1982 Program Management Costs (PA 828-980), 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - USIAP/HRG -- FY 1982 Attachment File -- Re: Occupational Segregation Meeting for FF Staff (PA 82-980), 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - USIAP/HRG -- FY 1982 Consultants -- H. Gordon Skilling Report on Helsinki Watch Committee (PA 82-980), 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - United States and International Affairs Program/International Affairs (USIAP/IA) -- FY 1982 Program Support Management Costs (PA 828-980) (Box 17, Folder 10)